Finding Aid of the Society of American Archivists Records, 1935-2016
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
- Records, 1935-2016, UWM Manuscript Collection 172; 271.9 cubic ft. (385 boxes, including 16 audio cassettes and 33 videocassettes) 1 oversize folder 7,545 digital files (26.2 GB) 1 film reel 5 microfilm reels approximately 170 books and serial titles
  - 5. Council Records and Member Files, 1935-1992, 200/05
    - 10. Richard J. Cox, 1987-1990, 200/05/10; 1 cubic ft. (1 box)
      - Council Meeting, 1988 September (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
      - Council Meeting, 1989 February (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Council Meeting, 1989 June (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
      - Council Meeting, 1989 October (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Council Updates and Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Executive Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
      - Executive Director, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Goals and Priorities, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - International Archival Affairs, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Membership Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Nominating Committee, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Publications Sub-Committee, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Task Force on Archives and Society, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 11. James O'Toole, 1988-1992, 200/05/11; .2 cubic ft. (1 box)
      - Council Correspondence, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Council Meeting Minutes, 1988-1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 6. Executive Director, 1959-2005, 200/06
    The executive director manages the programs, activities, and staff of SAA. S/he keeps the minutes of SAA and Council, prepares and mails notices, presents an annual report of the activities of SAA, manages the general operating budget, and performs such other duties as may be directed by Council. Notable topics in this record subgroup include the annual meeting; the American Archivist editorial office; regional and international archival organizations; SAA units, staff, Council and executive committee; professional organizations affiliated with SAA; and grants and special projects.
    Includes official news items and press releases posted by the organization on its website and annual reports, containing information on activities, professional development offerings, financial status, and membership trends.
    This record subgroup was originally arranged into groups corresponding to the terms of SAA executive directors. These groups were further arranged into series such as committee files, general files, and general correspondence. Following SAA's donation of its archives to UW-Milwaukee in April 2001, arrangement based upon individual executive director was discontinued. Additions to this subgroup are now arranged into series of administrative files, general correspondence, executive committee correspondence, Council files, and SAA units files. Researchers are advised to consult files in each arrangement scheme for full documentation of an executive director.
    - 1. Robert M. Warner, 200/06/01
      - 1. Committee Files, 1972-1973, 200/06/01/01; 2 cubic ft. (2 boxes)
        - AHA-OAH-SAA Joint Committee on Historians and Archives, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - Archives of Science (Box 1, Folder 4)
        - Archives-Library Relationships (ad Hoc) (Box 1, Folder 3)
        - Audio-Visual Records (Box 1, Folder 5)
        - Auditing (Box 1, Folder 6)
        - Awards (Box 1, Folder 7)
        - Buildings and Technical Equipment (Box 1, Folder 8)
        - Buildings and Technical Services (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Buildings and Technical Services-Survey Tally (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Business Archives (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Business Archives (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Church Archives (Box 1, Folder 10)
        - Collecting Personal Papers and Manuscripts (Box 1, Folder 11)
        - College and University Archives (Box 1, Folder 12)
        - Data Archives and Machine-Readable Records (Box 1, Folder 13)
        - Education and Training (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - Federal and State Governmental Relations (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Final Reports (Box 1, Folder 2)
        - Financial Development (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - General (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - Gondos Awards (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - International Archival Affairs (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - Labor Archives (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Local Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Membership Development (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Nominating (Election Materials) (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Oral History (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Paper Research (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Paper Research (ad Hoc) (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Preservation Methods (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Professional Standards (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Program (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Program
          - Background Materials (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Chairman's File (Box 2, Folder 7)
          - General and Copy for Printed Program (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Local Arrangements, Exhibits, Advertisements (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Reaction to Columbus, Ohio Meeting, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Session Coordinators File (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - Session Summaries (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Suggestions for Sessions (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Records Management (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Reference, Access, and Photo duplication Policies (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - State and Local Records (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - Status of Women in the Archival Profession (ad Hoc) (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Symposia and Regional Activity, Coordinating (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Techniques for Control and Description of Archives and Manuscripts (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Terminology (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - Urban Affairs (Box 1, Folder 34)
        - Urban and Industrial Archives (Dissolved 12/28/72) (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - 2. General Files, 1969-1973, 200/06/01/02; 1.4 cubic ft. (2 boxes)
        - American Archivist, General, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
        - American Council of Learned Societies, Endowment, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 14)
        - AHA Review Board, Questionnaire, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
        - Annual Meeting, 1972
          - Book Exhibit (Box 2, Folder 16)
          - Correspondence Regarding Program and Meeting (Box 2, Folder 17)
          - Local Arrangements (Box 2, Folder 18)
          - Program Committee (Box 2, Folder 19)
          - Program Sessions (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Archival Education Directory, Possible copy for edition, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - Budget, Executive Director's Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Church Bill, S. 1212, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Cline, Sylvia, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence, Miscellaneous: 1971 December-1972 April (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence, Miscellaneous: 1972 May-August (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - Correspondence, Miscellaneous: 1972 September-December (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - Correspondence, Miscellaneous: 1973 January-July (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - Council, 1972-1973
          - Applegate, Howard L., Treasurer (Box 1, Folder 44)
          - Berner, Richard C. (Box 1, Folder 46)
          - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 1, Folder 41)
          - Finch, C. Herbert (Box 1, Folder 47)
          - Freivogel, Elsie F. (Box 1, Folder 48)
          - General (Box 1, Folder 39)
          - Ham, F. Gerald, Vice President (Box 1, Folder 43)
          - Johnson, Edward M. (Box 1, Folder 49)
          - Kegan, Elizabeth Hamer (Box 1, Folder 50)
          - McCree, Mary Lynn (Box 1, Folder 51)
          - Minutes (Box 1, Folder 40)
          - Rhoads, James B. (Box 1, Folder 52)
          - Rundell, Walter, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 53)
          - Smith, Wilfred I., President (Box 1, Folder 42)
          - Warner, Robert M.-Executive Director (Box 1, Folder 45)
        - Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - Delaware Case, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        - Editorial Board, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 54)
        - Endowment Fund, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
        - Evans, Frank B.: Communications from, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Fellows, 1972 and 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
        - Forms Manual, Publication of, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
        - International Congress on Archives (Moscow), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
        - Koucky, Judith A., 1972 (Box 2, Folder 34)
        - Maine State Archives, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        - Membership
          - Brochure Texts, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
          - Deceased, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 37)
        - OAH-SAA Luncheon, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 55)
        - Organization of American States, Archival Project, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
        - Photo Preservation, Bibliographies, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 39)
        - Planning Corporation, Insurance Program, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 40)
        - Press Releases, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
        - St. Louis Area Archivists, Association of, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 42)
        - Tax Reform Legislation, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - 2. Judith A. Koucky (Acting Secretary), 200/06/02
      - 1. Committee Files, 1973-1974, 200/06/02/01; 1.4 cubic ft. (2 boxes)
        - Archives of Science (Box 1, Folder 18)
        - Archives-Library Relationships (Box 1, Folder 17)
        - ARMA-AREA, Proposal Joint Committee with SAA (Box 1, Folder 19)
        - Auditing (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - Aural and Graphic Records (Box 1, Folder 21)
        - Awards (Box 1, Folder 22)
        - Awards-Distinguished Service Award (Box 1, Folder 23)
        - Awards-Hamer Award (Box 1, Folder 24)
        - Bicentennial, ad hoc on the American Revolutionary (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Buildings and Technical Equipment (Box 1, Folder 26)
        - Business Archives (Box 1, Folder 27)
        - Church Archives (Box 1, Folder 28)
        - Collecting Personal Papers and Manuscripts (Box 1, Folder 29)
        - College and University Archives (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Data Archives and Machine-Readable Records (Box 1, Folder 31)
        - Education and Professional Development (Box 1, Folder 32)
        - Federal and State Governmental Relations (Box 1, Folder 33)
        - Genealogists, Proposed Joint Committee with (Box 1, Folder 34)
        - General (Box 2, Folder 1)
        - International Archival Affairs (Box 1, Folder 35)
        - Joint ALA-SAA (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Labor Archives (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Liaison Reports (Herbert Finch) (Box 2, Folder 5)
        - Local Arrangements (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Local Arrangements, 1976-Committee Appointments (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Manual for Committee Chairs (Box 2, Folder 2)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 15)
        - Nominating (Box 1, Folder 39)
        - Oral History (Box 1, Folder 40)
        - Paper Research (ad Hoc) (Box 1, Folder 41)
        - Preservation Methods (Box 1, Folder 42)
        - Professional Standards (Box 1, Folder 44)
        - Program (Box 1, Folder 43)
        - Publications Program, ad Hoc Committee to Develop (Box 1, Folder 45)
        - Records Management (Box 1, Folder 46)
        - Reference and Access Policies (Box 1, Folder 47)
        - Regional Archival Activity (Box 1, Folder 48)
        - Reports (Box 2, Folder 3)
        - Research and Development (Box 1, Folder 49)
        - Search Committee for Executive Director (Box 1, Folder 50)
        - State and Local Records (Box 1, Folder 51)
        - Statements of Purpose (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Status of Women, (ad Hoc) (Box 1, Folder 52)
        - Techniques for the Control and Description of Archives and Manuscripts (Box 1, Folder 53)
        - Terminology and Statistics (Box 1, Folder 54)
        - Urban Archives (Box 1, Folder 55)
      - 2. General Files, 1970-1974, 200/06/02/02; .4 cubic ft. (1 box)
        - Administrative Assistant, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
        - American Archivist
          - Advertising, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 45)
          - Bids, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
        - AHA, SAA Luncheon at Convention, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
        - Careers, Requests for Information on, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
        - Correspondence, Miscellaneous: 1973 July-1974 June (Box 1, Folder 49-50)
        - Council and Officers, Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 54)
        - Council Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 55)
        - Dues Increase, Membership Response to Proposed, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 51)
        - Expense Accounts, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 56)
        - Fellows, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 57)
        - Membership, Problems Concerning, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 52)
        - National Historic Records Program, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 53)
        - Weldon, Edward-Editor of American Archivist, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - 3. Ann Morgan Campbell, 200/06/03
      - 1. General Correspondence, 1974-1986, 200/06/03/01; 3 cubic ft. (3 boxes)
        - 1974
          - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 1)
        - 1975
          - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
        - 1976
          - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 4-6)
        - 1977
          - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Miscellaneous
            - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
        - 1978
          - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 10-13)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 14)
        - 1979
          - A-Z (Box 1, Folder 15-19)
          - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 20)
        - 1980
          - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
          - Miscellaneous
            - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 5)
            - Staff Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - 1981
          - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 7-9)
          - Miscellaneous
            - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
            - Staff Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 12)
        - 1982
          - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
        - 1982-1983
          - A-Z (Box 2, Folder 16-20)
        - 1984-1986
          - A-Z (Box 3, Folder 1-24)
      - 2. Council and Officers Files, 1974-1985, 200/06/03/02; 5 cubic ft. (5 boxes)
        - Council, 1974-1975
          - Rhoads, James B., President (Box 1, Folder 1)
          - Kegan, Elizabeth Hamer, Vice President (Box 1, Folder 2)
          - Applegate, Howard L., Treasurer (Box 1, Folder 3)
          - Council Minutes (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - Council Meeting Documents (Box 1, Folder 5)
          - Council/Annual Business Meeting Statements (1974) (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - General Correspondence of Council Members (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Weldon, Edward-Editor (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Coker, C.F.W.-Editor (Box 1, Folder 9)
        - Council, 1975-1976
          - Kegan, Elizabeth Hamer, President (Box 1, Folder 10)
          - Warner, Robert M., Vice President (Box 1, Folder 11)
          - Applegate, Howard L., Treasurer (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Council Minutes (Box 1, Folder 13)
          - General Correspondence of Council Members (Box 1, Folder 14)
          - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 15)
          - Coker, C.F.W., Editor (Box 1, Folder 16)
        - Council, 1976-1977
          - Warner, Robert M., President (Box 1, Folder 17)
          - Rundell, Walter, Vice President (Box 1, Folder 18)
          - Applegate, Howard L., Treasurer (Box 1, Folder 19)
          - McCree, Mary Lynn, Treasurer (Box 1, Folder 20)
          - Council Minutes (Box 1, Folder 21)
          - Business Meeting Minutes (1977) (Box 1, Folder 22)
          - General Correspondence of Council Members (Box 1, Folder 23)
          - Executive Committee (Box 1, Folder 24)
          - Annual Report (Box 1, Folder 25)
        - Council, 1977-1978
          - Rundell, Walter, President (Box 1, Folder 26)
          - Council Minutes (Box 1, Folder 27)
          - General Correspondence of Council Members (Box 1, Folder 28)
          - Executive Committee Correspondence (1977 June-December) (Box 1, Folder 29)
          - Coker, C.F.W., Editor (Box 1, Folder 30)
        - Council, 1978-1979
          - Committee on Publications (David Gracy) (Box 1, Folder 31)
          - Taylor, Hugh, President (Box 1, Folder 32)
          - Brichford, Maynard, Vice President (Box 1, Folder 33)
          - McCree, Mary Lynn, Treasurer (Box 1, Folder 34)
          - General Correspondence of Council Members (Box 1, Folder 35)
          - Purdy, Virginia C., Editor (Box 1, Folder 36)
        - Council, 1974 and 1975: General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 37)
        - Council, 1976: General Correspondence (Box 1, Folder 38)
        - Council: General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 39-40)
        - Council: General Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
        - Council: General Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
        - Council: Executive Committee Correspondence, 1978 and 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
        - Council: Council and Executive Committee Minutes, 1980-1982; Business Meeting Minutes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
        - Council Committee on Publications (Edmund Berkeley, Jr.-Chair), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
        - Council Committee on Policy (Frank Burke-Chair), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
        - Council Committee on Programs (Paul McCarthy-Chair), 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 10)
        - Council, 1979-1980
          - Brichford, Maynard, President (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Helmuth, Ruth W., Vice President (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - McCree, Mary Lynn, Treasurer (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - General Correspondence of Council Members (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Purdy, Virginia C., Editor, American Archivist (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - Campbell, Ann Morgan, Executive Director (Box 2, Folder 16)
        - Annual Business Meeting Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17-18)
        - Council Meeting Minutes, 1982 January 23-25 (Box 2, Folder 19)
        - Council Meeting Minutes, 1982 May 22-24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
        - Council Meeting Minutes, 1982 October 17 (Box 2, Folder 21)
        - Council Meeting Minutes, 1982 October 22 (Box 2, Folder 22)
        - Council Meeting Minutes, 1983 October 2 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        - Campbell, Ann Morgan and SAA, Memorandum of agreement Between, 1984 May 20 (Box 2, Folder 24)
        - Council Meeting, 1982 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 25)
        - Council Meeting, 1983 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 26)
        - Council Meeting, 1983 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 27)
        - Council Correspondence 1980 January-June (Box 2, Folder 28-29)
        - Council Correspondence, 1980 July-December (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
        - Council Correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 3-6)
        - Council Correspondence, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 7-10)
        - Council Correspondence, 1983 January-August (Box 3, Folder 11-13)
        - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - Council Committee on Policy, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 15)
        - Council Minutes, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 16)
        - Council Committee on Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 17)
        - Executive Committee Minutes, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 18)
        - Executive Committee Correspondence, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
        - Council Mailings, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
        - Council Minutes, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        - Council Mailings, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 22)
        - Council Subcommittee on Committees and Representatives, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
        - Subcommittees, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
        - SAA Council Meeting, 1985 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 25)
        - SAA Council Meeting, 1985 June 7 (Box 3, Folder 26)
        - Subcommittee/Consultants (Box 3, Folder 27)
        - Ballot Count-Officers and Council, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
        - Gracy Testimony-Committee of Government Operations U.S. House of Representatives (Box 3, Folder 29)
        - Edmund Berkeley, Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - Ann Morgan Campbell, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - Shonnie Finnegan, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - Meyer Fishbein, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Robert Gordon, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Ruth W. Helmuth, President, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        - Richard H. Lytle, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Paul H. McCarthy, Jr., 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - Mary Lynn McCree, Treasurer, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - Virginia Purdy, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Ed Weldon, President, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 11)
        - J. Frank Cook, Vice President, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        - Paul H. McCarthy, Jr., Treasurer, 1981- 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
        - Lynn Bonfield, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 14)
        - Shonnie Finnegan, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 15)
        - Paul McCarthy, Treasurer, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
        - Ann Morgan Campbell, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
        - Larry Hackman, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
        - William Joyce, 1981-1983 (Box 4, Folder 19)
        - Virginia Purdy, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
        - Sue Holbert, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
        - J. Frank Cook, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
        - David B. Gracy Vice-President, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
        - Executive Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
        - Council, 1983-1984
          - Gracy, David B-President, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 26)
          - Executive Committee (Box 4, Folder 27)
          - Duckett, Kenneth W. (Box 4, Folder 28)
          - Abraham, Terry, Projects Editor (Box 4, Folder 29)
          - Budget, Fiscal Year l985 (Box 4, Folder 30)
          - Correspondence, 1983 September-1984 February (Box 4, Folder 31)
          - Correspondence, 1984 March-August (Box 4, Folder 32)
          - Council Meeting, 1983 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 33)
          - Council Meeting, 1984 January 27-29 (Box 4, Folder 34)
          - Council Meeting, 1984 May 18-21 (Box 4, Folder 35-36)
          - Council Meeting, 1984 June (Box 4, Folder 37)
          - Council Meeting,1984 August 29 (Box 4, Folder 38)
          - Reports (Box 4, Folder 39)
        - Council, 1984-1985
          - Hinding, Andrea, President (Box 4, Folder 40)
          - Finnegan, Shonnie, Vice President (Box 4, Folder 41)
          - McCarthy, Paul, Treasurer (Box 4, Folder 42)
          - Fleckner, John A. (Box 4, Folder 43)
          - Hackman, Larry (Box 4, Folder 44)
          - Henry, Linda (Box 4, Folder 45)
          - Holbert, Sue (Box 4, Folder 46)
          - Joyce, William (Box 4, Folder 47)
          - Executive Committee (Box 4, Folder 48)
          - Campbell, Ann Morgan, Executive Director (Box 4, Folder 49)
          - Correspondence, 1984 September-December (Box 4, Folder 50)
          - Correspondence, 1985 January-July (Box 4, Folder 51)
          - Meeting, 1984 September 2 (Box 5, Folder 1)
          - Meeting, 1985 January 25-27 (Box 5, Folder 2)
          - Meeting, 1985 June 7-9 (Box 5, Folder 3)
          - Reports (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Council, 1985-1986
          - Finnegan, Shonnie, President (Box 5, Folder 5)
          - Joyce, William L., Vice President (Box 5, Folder 6)
          - Diffendal, Anne, Treasurer (Box 5, Folder 7)
          - Executive Committee (Box 5, Folder 8)
          - Hackman, Larry J. (Box 5, Folder 9)
          - Hedlin, Edie (Box 5, Folder 10)
          - Campbell, Ann Morgan, Executive Director (Box 5, Folder 11)
          - Raymond, Andrew, Program Officer (Box 5, Folder 12)
          - Duckett, Ken, Editorial Board (Box 5, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 14)
          - Meeting, 1985 October 27 (Box 5, Folder 15)
          - Meeting, 1985 November 2 (Box 5, Folder 16)
          - Meeting, 1986 February 14-16 (Box 5, Folder 17)
          - Meeting, 1986 June 13-15 (Box 5, Folder 18)
          - Business Meeting, 1985 Annual Meeting (Box 5, Folder 19)
          - Reports (Box 5, Folder 20)